之前  我们看到可以向display方法传递一个整形参数
Earlier, we saw that we could pass a number into the display method.
接下来我们进一步聊聊方法的输入和输出的不同
Let's talk more about the different inputs and output of a method.
我们来看一下MainActivity里的submitOrder方法
Let's look at the submitOrder method in the MainActivity as an example.
比如在这个方法中你有一堆代码
Say you have a bunch of lines of code in that method.
当用户点击Order按钮的时候
When the user clicks on the Order button,
按钮会触发这个submitOrder方法
it will trigger this submitOrder method to be called.
Android设备会将这些指令从头到尾运行一遍
The Android device will execute each of these instructions from top to bottom,
当它调用calculatePrice方法时  它会
and when it hits the calculatePrice method call it will
跳到calculatePrice方法被定义的地方
jump over to where the calculatePrice method is defined.
比如这个方法被定义在MainActivity文件的结尾
Say that this is defined at the bottom of the MainActivity file.
Android设备会从头到尾运行每一句指令
The Android device will execute each of these instructions from top to bottom of
然后它会自动跳回submitOrder方法
the method, and then it will jump back to the submitOrder method.
然后  它会继续运行指令直到
Then, it will continue executing these instructions until it hits the end
方法的结尾
of the method.
当calculatePrice方法被调用的时候
When the calculatePrice method is called,
我们可以传递一堆输入参数
we can pass a bunch of inputs over so
这样当我们运行这些代码的时候  我们可以使用这些输入数据
that when we're executing these lines of code, we can use these input values.
As a result of this method,
we can pass a single output value back to the caller.
That way, the output value can be used in the subsequent lines of code.
In Java, we call the inputs to a method input parameters, and
we can have zero or more input parameters.
In Java, we call the output a return value,
and we can have zero or one return value.
An example of an input parameter is passing the quantity
over to the calculatePrice method.
That way, this method can use the quantity to figure out the total price
of the whole order.
Then, we can pass that total price back as a return value.
And then in the submitOrder method, down here,
we can use this total price to do other things, like display it onscreen, or
create receipt, or anything like that.
So to summarize, this is where we define the calculatePrice method, and
this is where we call it.
We want to create a method to calculate the price of a coffee order.
Currently, we calculate the price directly in the submitOrder method, but
the logic to calculate the price is going to get a little more complicated.
So let's move it into its own method.
Then we can call it as many times as we want without copying and
pasting the code everywhere.
As you gain more experience in Android development, you'll gain better judgment
on when to create a new method for something or when you don't need to.
This will just come with more experience and more time.
So, this is the first time we're going to be creating
a new method in the MainActivity on our own.
Instead of starting by writing it from scratch, we want to start by learning to
recognize what is a correct method by reading some code snippets.
So in the instructor notes, we're going to provide you three options.
Read over these three code snippets and determine which
option correctly implements the method to calculate the price of the order.
When you click on the link in the instructor notes,
you'll see this just has code for options A, B, and C.
The goal here is for
you to become comfortable with reading code that you've never seen before.
We haven't gone over the exact rules for what makes a valid method, but
I want you to make your best guess on which option you think is most correct.
I also encourage you to Google search for
more information on how to define Java methods.
As you click through the different search results,
you'll come across information in the documentation that you don't understand.
But I want you to become comfortable with not understanding everything on
those pages, because it's perfectly normal to not understand everything.
All you need to do is just skim the articles for what you understand and
what you think is relevant to the problem at hand.
So, go ahead and read the code for
these three options, look up some information online, and then make your
best guest on how to correctly define the calculatePrice method.